I thought you said you were dizzy recently
你不是说最近头晕
And intermittent pain
还间歇性疼痛
Why didn't you tell her that
这些你怎么没告诉她呀
If it's okay free at kisskh.me
要是没事
Why worry her
干嘛让她担心
If something happens
要是有事
It's no use worrying about her
她担心也没用啊
Thrombotic heart failure
血栓心衰
Thrombolytic conservative treatment
溶栓保守治疗
The harm is less
危害要小一点
But not necessarily
但不一定
Can completely solve the problem
能彻底解决问题
There is a risk of thrombus shedding
有血栓脱落的风险
Surgery can
手术可以
Thoroughly treat vascular necrosis
彻底治疗血管坏死
But your physical condition
但你的身体状况
It's not good at all
本来就不好
There may be other risks
有可能会并发其他危险
Hello, your courier
您好 您的快递
Thank you
谢谢你
Have a good life
生活愉快
Walk slowly
慢走啊
Get an injection before eating
吃饭先打针
How did the copywriter do it
文案怎么做的
Ah
啊
Since Sister Colan left,
自从可岚姐走了之后
The temper guide is getting worse and worse
导脾气可越来越差了
After the last location
上次外景以后
Yu always doesn't come to the program very often
余总就不常来节目了
I just don't want Sister Colan
就是不想让可岚姐
Come into contact with the guide again
再接触导了吧
Listen to "what to eat" said the man over there
听"吃什么"那边人说
Sister Kelan and Yu Hao
可岚姐和余昊
It's about to be made public
就要公开了
Then we have two days
那我们这两天
Do you want to take a leave of absence
要不要请个假
What are you doing again
又干嘛
Didn't I tell you
我不是跟你说了
Don't give it to me all day
没事别成天给我
Hurry up and be in a hurry
赶紧 急事
Come quickly
快来
One hundred thousand urgent
十万火急
Deadly
要命
Come and sit down
来 坐
Today, Sister Bi made a reservation to celebrate
今天碧姐包场庆祝一下
What
啥
Our family Hao Hao
我们家昊昊
In my villa in the same neighborhood
在我同一个小区的别墅
Bought a house
买了房子
Walk from my home
距离我家步行
It only takes five minutes
只要五分钟
Five minutes yo
五分钟呦
Cheers
干杯
He bought it for Su Kelan
他那是买给苏可岚
And Mother Sue
和苏妈妈
They will live in a new home together in the future
以后他们一块住的新家
What are you happy about
你有什么可高兴的
Then I don't care
那我不管
Where can he buy it
他买哪不行
Just buy next door to me
就买我隔壁
That clearly implies that
那分明就在暗示
Hint
暗示
Drink
喝酒
Eat
吃饭啊
Come
来
Finish eating and drinking
吃完喝完
Go with me to buy some lamps
陪我去买点灯具
I want to hang it on the outer wall
我要挂在外墙
And the garden
还有花园
I'm going to make my home
我要让我的家
Become a whole community
变成全小区
The brightest building
最亮的一栋楼
So Hao Hao comes back every day
这样昊昊每天回来
You can see me
就可以看到我了
Will you be clear-headed
你脑子清醒一点好不好
All along
一直以来
You're all alone
都是你一个人
I'm talking to myself
在自说自话
Blind thinking for oneself
自己瞎想
In addition to Yu Hao in your mind,
你脑子里除了余昊
Can you decorate something else
能不能装点别的
Can you have a little life of your own
能不能有点自己的生活
Don't give you any more
别再为你一些
Thoughts at sixes and sevens all day long
成天乱七八糟的思想
Pull me out
把我拉出来
Have the time
有这时间
Isn't it good to read more books
多读读书不好吗
Don't let people laugh at you forever
别让人永远嘲笑
Aren't you stupid
你笨不好吗
What did you say about me
你 你说我啥
I said you have no brains
我说你没脑子
Love oneself and bring disgrace to oneself
自作多情 自取其辱
Do you know what it means
懂什么意思吗
What does the idiom bring disgrace to oneself mean
成语自取其辱什么意思
Why don't I explain it to you
要不然我给你解释一下
Original
原来
That's how you always see me
你一直是这么看我的
Then you still listen to me all day
那你还成天听我的
Change the image
改形象
Run around with me
跟我一起跑来跑去
Be sick
有病啊
Or do you think I'm a fool
还是你觉得我是个傻子
It's fun to be busy, isn't it
忙来忙去好玩是吗
And I've been busy for so long
而且我忙了这么久
Am I doing it for myself
我是为了我自己吗
Do I spend all my time
我是不是所有时间
It's all for you
都是为了你
You said I was flattered
你说我自作多情
What about you
你呢
Chatter and chatter
叽叽歪歪
I can't say a word I like
一句喜欢都说不出口
As soon as people refuse you,
人一拒绝 你就
You're awesome, you're smart
你牛你聪明
I'm stupid
我是傻
But at least I'm sincere
但至少我真诚
I can try
我可以努力
Than some
总比某些
A bag that will only hide in the corner
只会躲在角落里的     包
Much better, huh
强多了吧
Is Sister Bi better
碧姐 导好些了吗
The guide is in a bad mood today
导今天心情不好
It's just you who talk to him
也就你找他聊
He can be in a better mood
他都能心情好些
It's up to you to comfort him
靠你安慰他了
Why are you following me
你跟着我干嘛
I'm sorry
对不起
Don't you crocodile
你别假惺惺的了
Didn't you always
你不是一直
Treat me like a joke
把我当个笑话看吗
Just telling the truth
只是说了实话而已
There's nothing to apologize for
没什么好道歉的
I'm not
我不是
Actually, I'm the one who's stupid
其实傻的人是我
I'm just taking it out on you
我只是迁怒你
I want to let myself
我希望让自己
Don't appear so incompetent
不要显得那么无能
That's why we belittle
所以才贬低
And deny all your efforts
和否认你所有的努力
I'm not just stupid
我不只傻
Still incompetent
还无能
Come on
少来
You just call me stupid
你就说我蠢
Said I was flattered
说我自作多情
Bring disgrace to oneself
自取其辱
You're not stupid
你不蠢
Every idiom you just said
你刚才说的每一个成语
None of them are wrong
没有一个是错的
Do you think this way
你觉得这样
Is comfort appropriate
安慰人合适吗
I'm sorry
对不起
Thank you
谢谢你
Comfort me
安慰我
You will know that you are fierce with me
你就知道凶我
Fierce me, fierce me
凶我 凶我
You think
你以为
I don't know myself
我不知道自己
Is it self-love
是自作多情吗
You think
你以为
I don't know
我不知道
Surely Yu Hao won't like me
余昊肯定不会喜欢我吗
I just want to make
我就是想让
Be happy yourself
自己开心一点
I don't want to be so sad
我不想那么难过
I'll lie to myself and say
我就会骗自己说
Diamond
张碧
You will have hope
你会有希望的
You just have to work hard
你只要努力
It will pay off free at kisskh.me
就会有回报的
I just want every day
我只想让每天
Everyone is happy
都开开心心的呀
Am I wrong
我有错吗
I'm like this
我这样
Is it really stupid
是不是真的挺蠢的
Won't
不会
You're the one I've ever seen
你是我见过
Most sincere
最真诚
The person who works the hardest
最努力的人
Those who deny you
那些否定你的人
It's all because
都是因为
They can't do it by themselves
他们自己做不到
So I hope to see your jokes
所以希望看到你的笑话
Just like me
就像我一样
It's all
都是
They are all particularly bad ideas
都是特别差劲的想法
You don't have to worry about this
你也不用为这些
Sad at a bad eye
差劲的眼光而难过
Because when one day
因为当有一天
You run farther
你跑得更远
When flying higher,
飞得更高的时候
They'll all envy you
他们都会羡慕你
Really
真的吗
Come on, come on
来来来
Today, Jin Dao and Bi Jie
今天金导和碧姐
Invite everyone to dinner together
一起请大家吃饭
Thank you, sister Bi
谢谢碧姐
Where's Jin Dao
金导呢
What's the matter with you
你怎么回事啊
I thought we agreed to have dinner together
不是说好一起吃饭的吗
And said he wanted to apologize
还说要道歉
What's going on
怎么回事
It's for you
给你的
You
你
Didn't I say before
之前不是说
Dislike
不喜欢
Is it in front of the mobile phone
手机前置的吗
Just
就
No, it won't
不会啊
Like it very much
很喜欢
That's good
那就好
Let's eat
吃饭吧
Eat and sit down
吃饭快坐
I said you do this
我说就你做这个
Particularly delicious
特别好吃
Time for dinner
吃饭了
Ah good
啊好
Sit down quickly, sister Bi
你快坐 碧姐
It's made by delicious sister Bi
就是好吃 碧姐做的
Eat more if it is delicious
好吃就多吃点
Is that the guide has done too little
就是导做的太少了
Just one dish
就一个菜
Pick up Kelan's mother on the way
顺路捎可岚妈妈
Go to the hospital for an examination
去医院做检查
You won't have to join in the fun
你就不用凑热闹了
I have to continue to be a strategist for you
我得继续给你当军师啊
Although Hao Hao and I
虽然我跟昊昊
There is no hope
没什么希望了
But Su Kelan's mother
但是苏可岚妈妈
I like you
喜欢你啊
I asked you to go to the hospital for examination
都让你去医院做检查了
Prove that you want to be a son-in-law more
证明更想让你当女婿嘛
Besides, Su Kelan
再说了苏可岚
Care so much about mom
那么在意妈妈
Mother's opinion is of course important
妈妈的看法当然重要了
You still have a good chance of winning
你的胜算还是很大的
Wait for me
等等我嘛
Aunt
阿姨
What's the matter
怎么了
No one
没人吗
The door is unlocked
门没锁呀
Why don't you go in and have a look
要不然进去看看
I'm coming in
我进来了啊
Let's just go in and wait
我们直接进去等
It would be nice if you didn't
不就好了
Aunt
阿姨
What happened to Auntie
阿姨怎么了
Rise up
扶起来
Don't move, don't move
别动别动
Can't move
不能动
Call Su Kelan
给苏可岚打电话
I'll call 120
我打120
Overdose of insulin
多打了胰岛素
Causing hypoglycemia
造成血糖过低
Life is in danger now
现在有生命危险
But Lan still can't get in touch
可岚还是联系不上
How do you do
您好
The number you dialed is turned off
您所拨打的电话已关机
Sister Kelan
可岚姐
You are thinking of meeting Yang Zong
你这是想到要见杨总
Be nervous
紧张了
It's really a little
真是有点
Nothing
没事
Our gift
咱们的礼物
Someone has been arranged
已经安排人
It was delivered in advance
提前送过去了
Reach out and don't hit smiling faces
伸手不打笑脸人
No matter how fierce the investor is, he is also a human being
再凶的投资人也是人嘛
Since you are still
既然你还是
If you are so nervous,
这么紧张的话
Or we'll go home
要不咱们就打道回府
Don't go
别去了吧
OK, let Yang Zhen
行啊 让杨振
And feel what it means
也感受一下什么叫
The feeling of not being seen by others
不被人待见的感觉
Dear travelers and friends
亲爱的旅客朋友们
We have safely
我们已经安全地
Fly to a destination
飞抵目的地
When disembarking
下机时
Please take all your luggage with you
请带好全部行李物品
Not Yu Zong's side
不是余总那边
Is there anything going on
有什么情况吧
Feed gold guide
喂 金导
Colan
可岚
Sister Kelan, what's wrong with you
可岚姐 你怎么了
Sister Kelan, are you all right
可岚姐 你没事吧
Sister Kelan, don't scare me
可岚姐 你别吓我呀
Sister Kelan
可岚姐
Squeeze what squeeze ah
挤什么挤啊
Colan
可岚
Colan, your mother
可岚 你妈妈
How do you do
您好
A plane ticket home
回家的机票
Could you speak up, Miss
小姐您能大点声吗
I want to change my air ticket home
我要改回家的机票
Where is your home
您家在哪里啊
Chongqing
重庆
What time is it
几点的
Fastest
最快的
May I have your identification, please
麻烦出示一下您的证件
Did you drop it
是掉了吗
You can go to the third floor
您可以去三楼
Go through the temporary ID card
办理一下临时身份证
How do you do? Is this Yao Qian
您好 是姚茜吗
Ah yes
啊是
This is Zhao Zhao from Shanghai Company
我是上海公司的赵赵
Where's your Sue
你们苏总呢
How do you do, madam
女士 您好
Excuse me, are you not feeling well
请问您不舒服吗
The investors will be here soon
投资人马上就到了
Do you think we should go first
你看要不要我们先去
All right
好吧
Diamond
张碧
Mr. Shi called you
石总 给您电话
Lao Wu
老吴
Investment in "What to Eat"
“吃什么”的投资
I inquired about the situation
我打听了一下情况
I think we should be cautious.
觉得还是应该谨慎一点
I met Yu Hao
我见过余昊
And his team
和他的团队了
It should be reliable
应该是靠谱的
How about this
这样吧
I arranged for you
我安排你
Meet them, too
跟他们也见个面
All right
好吧
Contact Mr. Su
联系一下苏总
Tell her to arrange it as soon as possible
让她尽快安排
Yu Hao and Wu Dong meet
余昊和吴董见个面
OK
好的
My interview is over
我采访已经结束了
What's the situation over there
你那边什么情况
Yu Zong's investors have arrived
余总 投资人都到了
But Sister Colan
但是可岚姐
I don't know where I went
不知道去哪了
People are gone
人不见了
I'll be right there
我马上来
Hello, the number you dialed
您好 您所拨打的电话
Shut down
已关机
Xiaoyan Airport
小闫 机场
Ladies and gentlemen
女士们 先生们
The plane is about to arrive
飞机即将到达
Beautiful "Mountain City" Chongqing
美丽的“山城”重庆
How's Auntie
阿姨怎么样
Still being rescued
还在抢救
Colan has already called me back
可岚已经回过我电话了
Is rushing back
正在往回赶
Yang Zong
杨总
This way
这边
Colan
可岚
My mother
我妈
How's my mom
我妈怎么样
Who is Villi's family
谁是李慧家属
This
这
Please sign here
请在这里签个字
It's okay, Kelan
没事可岚
I'm sure I can save it
肯定救得回来
This is the normal process of the hospital
这是医院正常流程
Thank you, Doctor
谢谢医生
Good
好
The number you dialed
您拨叫的号码
There is no answer for the time being
暂时无人接听
Colan
可岚
Dr. Wang, how is my mother
王医生 我妈妈怎么样
I got an extra shot of insulin
胰岛素多打了一支
Severe hypoglycemia causes shock
严重低血糖造成休克
It's a good thing he was in time
还好他及时
Take your mother to the hospital
把你妈送到医院
Thank you
谢谢
Is there any problem with thrombosis and heart failure
血栓心衰有没有问题
Thrombotic heart failure
血栓心衰
The last time your mother had dialysis,
上回你妈做透析的时候
Your friend came with her
是你朋友陪她来的
Thrombosis and heart failure were detected
检查出有血栓心衰
After getting out of danger
脱离危险后
You think about it
你考虑一下
Do you put your body
是不是把身体
After raising it,
养好了以后
Have the operation done
把手术给做了
Colan
可岚
Your mother is in poor health
你妈身体不好
No matter how busy you are, you should care
你再忙也要关心
Spend more time with her
多陪陪她
You came with my mother
你陪我妈妈来的
You know she's not doing well
你知道她情况不好
Why didn't you tell me
你为什么不告诉我
I'm sorry, Colan
对不起 可岚
I thought
我以为
Why didn't you tell me
你为什么不告诉我
Your own mother
你自己的妈
You don't care enough
你关心不够
Someone else has helped you so much
别人帮你这么大忙
And you yell at people
你还对人吼
I'm sorry
对不起
Colan
可岚
What time is it
这都几点了
Haven't come yet
还没来
Yeah
是啊
Can't keep putting us
不能一直把我们
Let's hang it here
晾在这吧
That's right
就是啊
Excuse me, bosses
不好意思啊 各位老板
Our Su Zong
我们苏总
Sue, she suddenly came out
苏总她突然出了
A matter of great urgency
一件很紧急的事
I
我
Xiaoyao is fine
小姚 没事
You've said it many times
你已经说了很多遍了
How about this
这样吧
Let's eat first and wait
我们先吃着等等
Yu Hao should be here soon
余昊应该也快到了
Good
好
This
这
What's the situation here
这什么情况
Didn't she invite us
不是她请我们吗
Right
对呀
Yu Hao said
余昊说
She is ill
她生病了
Be ill
生病了
She has our number
她有我们的电话呀
Now that she is ill,
既然她生病了
It's time to talk to all of us
也该跟我们大家
Just say hello in advance
事先打个招呼才行啊
I'm really sorry
真的不好意思啊
Colan, she said temporarily
可岚她临时说
Not feeling well
身体不太舒服
So I've kept you waiting
所以让各位久等了
I'm sorry for her
我替她跟大家说声抱歉
Come and eat, eat
来 吃吧吃吧
Yu Hao
余昊
You are a vice president
你这个副总啊
You'd better be careful
你还是谨慎一点好
What, be careful
什么谨慎点
I shouldn't have used this man at all
根本就不该用这个人
Yu Hao
余昊
We started our business from you
我们从你创业
Invest in the capital from the beginning
一开始就入资
I'm optimistic about you because I've always been
看好你是因为一直以来
You are a very rational person
你都是一个很理性的人
The company has developed to the present
公司发展到现在
You also gave a lot
你也付出了很多
But since this Su Kelan
可是自从这个苏可岚
After appearing
出现之后
You become confused
你就变得脑子不清楚
Yes
是
You fall in love
你谈恋爱
We have no reason to interfere
我们没有理由干涉
But you've been in love
可是你恋爱已经
Seriously affected the operation
严重影响了经营
Do you know
你知道吗
Seriously affect the operation
严重影响经营
Which number do you come from
各位是从哪个数字
See it
看出来
I influenced the operation
我影响经营了
Yu Hao
余昊
I'm going to do as you do
要照你这么做下去
That will definitely be affected
那肯定是会受影响的
Who is Su Kelan
苏可岚是个什么人呢
Dare to send a circle of friends to force the palace
敢发朋友圈逼宫
You're really hooked up
你还真就上套
I told you she didn't send the video
我说了视频不是她发的
Good
好
You think it's us
你觉得是我们对她
It's biased, isn't it
有偏见是吧
So today is you
所以今天是你
Let her treat us to this meal
让她请我们吃的这个饭
But what about the result
可结果呢
Where are the people
人呢
Does she buy your account
她买你账吗
People don't look at character
用人也不看看人品
I just wanted to ask you
我就想问你们
What makes you judge
你们凭什么判断
She didn't come on purpose
她是故意不来的
And by what judgment
又凭什么判断
She has a bad character
她人品恶劣
Have you ever seen
你们有见过
Is her normal working ability
她平时的工作能力吗
Have you investigated
你们有调查过
Her performance level
她的业绩水平吗
You rely solely on some
你们单凭一些
Peach news and gossip
桃色新闻和流言蜚语
Just discredit a person
就这么抹黑一个人
You guys are like this
你们这样跟
Those keyboard men on the Internet
网上那些键盘侠
What's the difference
有什么区别
Yu Hao
余昊
Let's go out and talk
咱们俩出去聊一下
Just a moment
稍等
A lot of times I know
很多时候我知道
There are some words you don't like to hear
有些话你不爱听
It doesn't sound good either
也不好听
But those words
但是那些话
It all makes sense
都是有道理的
She's really sick
她真是因为生病
Didn't you come
才没来吗
Or you don't know where she is
还是你也不知道她在哪
Jin Dao
金导
I'm sorry
对不起
Just now
刚刚
I'm blaming myself
我是在怪我自己
Didn't take good care of my mother
没有照顾好我妈妈
Angry at you
迁怒了你
I'm really sorry
真的很抱歉
It is estimated that it will take a long time
估计还要等很久
Why don't I give it to everyone
要不我给大家
Order something to eat
叫点吃的吧
Sister Meng Kelan suddenly disappeared
梦姐 可岚姐突然不见了
Do you know where she went
你知道她去哪了吗
Hello Cece
喂 茜茜
Hello Sister Meng
喂 梦姐
Sister Kelan, did she find it
可岚姐她找着了吗
Something happened at her house
她家出了点事
Please, please
拜托你了
So say
所以说
You don't even know her
你根本就不了解她
Yu Hao
余昊
What the hell are you doing
你到底在搞什么呀
Are you all right
你没事吧
I'm okay
我没事
It's good to be okay
没事就好
Nothing
没事
Why did you suddenly disappear
你为什么突然消失啊
I didn't answer the phone either
电话也不接
What the hell
搞什么呀
I'm sorry. I
对不起啊我
Do you know or not
你到底知不知道
What are we doing here today
我们今天来干嘛的啊
Told me this morning
早上还跟我说
To stand people up
要放人家鸽子
Are you serious
你说真的是吗
Do you do this
有你这么干的吗
I know I
我知道 我
What do you know
你知道什么呀
Now Yang Zhen and all the directors
现在杨振和所有董事
Trust in you
对你的信任
Have completely dropped to freezing point
都已经完全降到了冰点
So you can come here at once
这样你现在立刻赶过来
We can still pull it over
我们还能扳过来
I can't come
我来不了
Why can't my mother come
我妈 怎么就来不了
Now everyone is waiting for you alone
现在所有人等你一个人
Do you know or not
你到底知不知道
Hello
喂
Su Kelan
苏可岚
Are you listening to me
你有没有在听我说话
What else is going on
到底还有什么事
Than the two of us
比我们两个人
Go forward together
一起往前走
More important
更重要
Hello
喂
Su Kelan
苏可岚
I said I couldn't come
我说了来不了
Don't you understand
你听不明白吗
Also
也是
Anyway, my business
反正我的事情
You don't want to hear it at all
你根本就不想听
Don't care
不关心
It's just your business
只有你的事情
Is the most important thing, isn't it
才是最重要的不是吗
My mother is critically ill
我妈妈病危
I'll be with you right away
我马上过来
What's the matter
怎么了
Su Kelan's mother is critically ill
苏可岚的妈妈病危
The investment thing
投资的事情
Forget it
就算了吧
Feeding stone chief
喂 石总
I've been looking for you all day
找了你一整天
Mr. Yu finally has time to call back
余总 终于有空回电话了
Excuse me, Mr. Shi
不好意思 石总
It's a little urgent today
今天的确有点急事
That Yu Hao
那个 余昊
I was supposed to be holding
我本来是顶着
Pressure from the board of directors
董事会的压力
Want to vote for you
想投你的
But all day long you guys
但你们一整天
I can't get in touch
都联系不上
Let me be in Lao Wu
让我在老吴
How to hang up that face
那面子怎么挂
People like you
你们这样的人
I don't want to cooperate
我不想合作
What time is it? I haven't come yet
这都几点了还没来
So long
这么久
I've been waiting for so long
等了这么久了
Excuse me
不好意思
It's urgent. I'll go first
有急事我先走了
I just heard that Sok Li stopped voting
我刚听说李石不投了
Yu Hao
余昊
I sympathize with her family emergency
她家里有急事我很同情
But you need to know who you are
但是你要知道你的身份
You're not only responsible for her
你不光要为她负责
You have to pay attention to all the
你还要对所有的
Investors are responsible
投资人负责
I've already said that
我刚才已经说过了
Su Kelan's mother is critically ill
苏可岚妈妈病危
Yu Hao has already flown back
余昊已经往回飞了
Out of danger
脱离危险了
Yu Hao
余昊
It was Yang Zhen who told you
是杨振告诉你
My flight information
我的航班信息吧
I really don't have time now
我现在真的没空
Let's talk about anything later
有什么事回头再说
If you really do
你要是真的
For the good of Su Kelan
为了苏可岚好
You just stop and listen to me
你就停下来听我说两句
Su Kelan's mother is critically ill
苏可岚妈妈病危
Everyone is sympathetic
大家都很同情
But Sok Li's investment
但是李石的投资
It's really because she can't help it
确实是因为她没有办法
Timely handling
及时处理
Yellow
黄了
If you don't deal with it
如果你再不处理
She really caused it
她就真的造成了
The loss of the company
公司的损失
How do you want her to talk to each other in the future
你让她以后怎么和
Get along with your partners
你的合作伙伴相处
How to get along with you
怎么和你相处
You go to Su Kelan now
你现在去找苏可岚
Her mother's illness
她的妈妈病情
It won't get better
也不会好转
But you deal with the problem now
但你现在立刻处理问题
There may be a remedy
或许还有补救的可能
But Sok Lee and I
可我跟李石
I didn't deal with it in the first place
本来就不对付
Don't look for him, look for Yun Teng
不找他 找云腾
Frank and I have a good personal relationship
弗兰克跟我私交很好的
I'll come back this time
我这次回来
I was supposed to help you match up
本来就是帮你们牵线的
I'll help you
我帮你
It's also to help her
也是帮她
Why don't you go back and get your things first
你先回去拿东西吧
I'm here
这里有我
I want to wait for my mother to wake up
我想等我妈醒过来
Why hasn't it arrived yet
怎么还没到
Check it out
查一下
What other disputes have occurred in the past three years
过去三年还有哪些纠纷
Find them all
全部都找出来
Confirmed
确认了
Tomorrow with Frank
明天和弗兰克
Meet in Beijing
在北京见面
Angie, book a trip for me
安捷 帮我订一趟
The earliest flight tomorrow
明天最早的航班
Good
好
I'll be busy with something urgent in the company first
我先在公司忙点急事
I'll meet you at the hospital later tomorrow
明天晚一点去医院找你
Angie, give me that file
安捷 把那个文件给我
Wake up
醒啦
Mengmeng, I'll make a phone call
梦梦 我去打个电话
Okay, go ahead
好 去吧
The number you dialed
您所拨叫的号码
There is no answer for the time being
暂时无人接听
It's over
完事了
Lawyer Lai Shao
来 邵律师
That
那个
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Stay up with me all night
陪我熬了一个通宵
Hard work
辛苦了
Nothing
没事
You're welcome
不用谢
It's all included in the working hours
都算工时费里面了
Go away
走了
Let me help you with it
我帮你弄一下
I think according to
我觉得按照
For this version,
这个版本来说
We can have
我们可以有
This modification
这个修改
It's okay. Why don't you go to work
没事 你去忙吧
I'm here free at kisskh.me
这里有我
Mr. Li
李总
In any case
无论如何
I will take Mr. Yu to see Wu Dong
我会带余总去见吴董的
Please rest assured
请您放心
There is still a while before the flight takes off
离航班起飞还有一阵
Let me check the documents for you again
我再帮你检查一下文件
You are a person who knocks the code carefully
你这个人就敲代码细致
Others are confused
其他的就稀里糊涂的
You see
你看
A brief account of your performance last year
你去年的业绩简述
Why is it so untidy
怎么做的这么潦草
Where is the scrawl
哪里潦草
Isn't it quite clear
不挺清楚吗
Just because you know doesn't mean others know
你清楚不代表别人清楚
How about a little attitude of being Party B
有点做乙方的态度好吗
I changed it for you
我帮你改了
Respect each other
要尊重对方
Reduce dyslexia
降低阅读障碍
You can't look past one side
你看不过去一边去
I'll change it myself while you go
你一边去我自己改
Then I'll check the others for you
那我帮你查其他的
Don't change it for me
你别给我乱改
I changed it. Can you see that
我改了你看得出来吗
If you have the ability, you can check it again
你有本事你就再查一遍
Hello
喂
Sister Kelan, I'm sorry
可岚姐 不好意思
I was in the company with Mr. Yu last night
昨晚和余总在公司
Work overtime all night
加了一晚上班
I fell asleep and didn't hear your call
睡着了 没听到你电话
Hard work
辛苦了
Excuse me
不好意思
Shi Zong
石总
Xiao Su
小苏
I know there is an accident at your home
我知道你家有意外情况
As a friend
作为朋友
I understand and sympathize with you
我很理解也同情你
I also wish your mother a speedy recovery
也祝你妈妈早日康复
But in business, we only look at the results
但生意场上只看结果
I hope to pick
我希望挑选
Emotionally stable partners
情绪稳定的合作伙伴
Mr. Shi, I'm sorry
石总 我很抱歉
I will definitely face to face
我一定会当面
To apologize to Wu Dong
去和吴董致歉的
Please give me another chance
请再给我一次机会
Wu Dong takes his family abroad for vacation
吴董带家人出国度假
Has already boarded the plane
已经登机了
Can you wait for him
那可否等他
I'll talk about it when I get back
回来的时候我再去说
I heard that Yu Hao's side
我听说余昊那边
I contacted Yun Teng through Shen Zhilin
通过沈之琳联系了云腾
Go to Beijing to talk to Frank today
今天去北京和弗兰克谈
Wish him all the best
祝他一切顺利吧
Don't you call me either
你也别给我打电话了
I need a rest
我需要休息
Shi Zong I
石总 我
You also take care of your family with peace of mind
你也安心照顾家人
Just like it says
就像上面写到的
What about our company
我们公司呢
Almost now
现在差不多
There are 480 employees
有480名员工
Bachelor degree or above accounted for 98.5%
本科以上学历占98.5%
And then our company's
然后我们公司的
What about concepts? Actually
概念呢其实
Colan
可岚
Your mother is in poor health
你妈身体不好
No matter how busy you are, you should care
你再忙也要关心
Spend more time with her
多陪陪她
Happy cooperation
合作愉快
Mr. Yu, this project
余总这个项目啊
Very good
非常的好
So expect us
那么期待我们
The next cooperation
接下来的合作
Let's go first
先走了
Yu Hao
余昊
Frank has an appointment
弗兰克约了
Friends have lunch together
朋友一起吃午饭
You're really not coming
你真的不来啊
Maybe next time. There's something urgent
下次吧 还有急事
We have to get back first
得先赶回去
Thank you today
今天谢谢你
Go back and bring Colan
回头带可岚
Invite you to dinner together
一起请你吃饭
I gotta go. It's gonna be late
我先走了 快晚点了
Colan
可岚
I'll do it
我来
No need
不用了
I'm sorry
对不起
I'm giving you trouble
给你添麻烦了
Nothing
没事
You just take care of your aunt with peace of mind
你只管安心照顾阿姨
Leave the company to me
公司的事交给我
Yu Hao
余昊
The position of vice president
副总裁这个职位
You hire someone new
你新招一个人吧
I know you are very tired these days
我知道你这段时间很累
So you can have a rest for a while
这样 你休息一段时间
When do you want to come back?
等你什么时候想回来了
Can you come back again
再回来好不好
I don't want to go back
我不想回去了
I can't imagine such a thing
我不敢想象这样的事情
Happened again
再发生一次
All right, during this time
好 这段时间
You can leave nothing to yourself
你可以什么都不用管
Just take care of your aunt with peace of mind
只管安心照顾阿姨
Good or not
好不好
I'm sorry
对不起啊
I overestimated my ability
是我高估了自己的能力
I took it
是我揽下
Such an important job
那么重要的工作
But it turns out to be trouble everywhere
结果却到处给人添麻烦
I gave my mother trouble
我给我妈添麻烦
Give Jin Xuan Diamond trouble
给金宣  张碧添麻烦
Give you trouble
给你添麻烦
I'll go up with you
我陪你上去
No need
不用了
I think
我想
We should calm down for a while
我们应该冷静一段时间
What do you mean
什么意思啊
Yu Hao
余昊
I don't want to love you anymore
我不想再因为爱你
Ignoring my mother
忽略了我妈
But I don't miss you either
可是我也不想你
To accommodate me
为了迁就我
Delayed your career
耽误了你的事业
I think we should
我想我们应该
Think it over again
再好好考虑一下
Our relationship
我们的关系
What do you mean
什么叫
Think about our relationship
好好想想我们的关系啊
I don't think we can
我觉得我们没法
Adapt to each other's rhythm
适应对方的节奏
Colan
可岚
Where else do I have
我到底还有哪里
Not doing well enough
做的不够好
You can tell me
你可以告诉我
There's nothing wrong with you
你没有哪里不好
It's just that we're different
只是我们不一样
I have a job
我明明有工作
But my mother
可是我妈妈
After something happened
出了事情以后
I can only take care of my mother
我只能顾得上我妈
And I know you care about me
我也知道你在意我
But you know
可是你知道
After what happened to my mother
我妈妈出了事情以后
You are the choice
你却是选择
Working with Shen Zhilin
和沈之琳一起工作
Have you been to the company
你去过公司
I did it for you
我那是为了你
I don't want the future
我不希望以后
You are embarrassed in front of Yang Zhen
你在杨振面前为难
And I don't want people at the company
我也不希望公司的人
Think the loss this time
认为这次的损失
You caused it
是你造成的
This is what you think is important
这是你觉得重要的事
But this is for me
可这对我来说
It doesn't matter at all
根本就不重要
Have you ever thought about
你有没有想过
What do I need
我需要的是什么
The most important thing for me
对我来说最重要的
It's mom
是妈妈
For you
对你来说
It's a career
是事业
In essence
从本质上
We are not the same kind of people
我们就不是一类人
Even if you barely go down now
就算现在勉强下去了
It will still be in the future
将来也还是会
What kind of person am I
我是哪类人
I used to
我之前
I have been afraid to accept this relationship
一直不敢接受这段感情
Because I'm afraid of failing you
因为我怕辜负你
You encouraged me
是你鼓励我
Let me take that step
让我迈出了那一步
I didn't take care of people before
我以前不会照顾人的
I will now
我现在会了
I used to
我以前
I don't know how to communicate with others
也不懂跟别人沟通
But I can now
但我现在可以
Chatting with your mother
和你妈妈聊天了
But you tell me
但是你却告诉我
We are not the same kind of people
我们不是一类人
I'm sorry I was wrong
对不起 是我错了
I underestimated it
是我看轻了
The difficulty of a relationship
一段感情的难度
What's the difficulty
什么难度啊
Colan
可岚
What happened to Auntie was an accident
阿姨的事是个意外
There will inevitably be accidents in life
生活难免会有意外
But it doesn't happen every day
但不是每天都有意外
Yu Hao, what do you like about me
余昊 你喜欢我什么
You like me
你喜欢我
Not because I can cook
不是因为我能做饭
Can take care of you
能照顾你
You like me
你喜欢的是我
Can help you in your career
能在事业上帮到你
What you like is a man
你喜欢的是一个
Covering everything
面面俱到
Can do anything
什么都能
Handled Su Kelan
处理好的苏可岚
I used to think
以前我也觉得
I can do it
我可以做到
But I was wrong. I can't do it
可是我错了我做不到
Love, it's actually
爱情它其实
Can't stand the test at all
根本经不起考验
I don't want one day in the future
我不想未来某一天
You'll blame me for not being able to do all this
你会怪我做不到这一切
Because it's simply
因为这根本
It's not who I am.
就不是我本来的样子
I'm sorry
对不起
In pairs
成对的
This place in the future
以后这个地方
It belongs only to me
只属于我
Good
好
Your mother has
你妈妈已经
Out of danger
脱离了生命危险
It needs more care
还需要多加照顾
My friend got in touch
我朋友联系了
Professor Sun from Union Medical College Hospital
协和医院的孙教授
Consult at any time if necessary
如果需要 随时会诊
Thank you, Jin Dao
谢谢你啊 金导
For my mother's sake
为了我妈妈的事
I've been busy all night
都忙了一个晚上了
It's okay
没事的
Don't think about anything
你什么都不要乱想
Auntie will definitely get better
阿姨一定会好起来的
Have you ever thought about
你有没有想过
What do I need
我需要的是什么
In essence
从本质上
We are not the same kind of people
我们就不是一类人
How's Auntie
阿姨怎么样了
Just woke up once
刚醒了一次
The doctor came to see
医生来看过
Nothing
没什么事
You blame him
你是怨他
Didn't come to you at the first time
没有第一时间过来找你
Angie told me everything
安捷都跟我说了
He's because
他是因为
I know
我知道
I don't blame him
我不怪他
Then why are you still like this
那你为什么还这样
He doesn't fit in with me
他和我在一起不合适
There is someone more suitable for him
有更适合他的人
Didn't I tell you
我不是跟你说了
He doesn't want you to take the blame
他是不想让你背锅
Cai and Shen Zhilin
才和沈之琳
What he loves is work
他热爱的是工作
He was with me at first
他最初和我在一起
It's not because I love my family
并不是因为我热爱家庭
But because of my effective work
而是因为我的工作得力
Clear organization
条理清晰
Isn't it
不是吗
But now I'm
可是我现在
I can't work either
也没法工作
There is no reason either
也没有理智了
This is temporary
这是暂时的
Even if this time is over,
就算这阵过去了
I don't want to be with him anymore
我也不想再和他
Together
在一起了
Why
为什么
My mother
我妈
A while ago
前一阵子
A thrombus was detected
查出了血栓
She didn't tell me
她没和我说
Dialysis was supposed to be
本来透析应该是
I went with her
我陪着她去的
Colan
可岚
Don't think about it
别多想
You were busy a while ago
前阵子你忙啊
What am I up to
我在忙什么
I'm just busy falling in love
我就是忙着谈恋爱
My mom, she didn't tell me
我妈她没告诉我
I am afraid of delaying me and Yu Hao
是怕耽误我和余昊
Don't get into a corner, okay
不要钻牛角尖好不好
It was an accident
这是意外
Auntie is out of danger
阿姨已经脱离危险了
It's all right now
现在没事了
It wasn't an accident
这不是意外
It's because I always patronize
是因为我老光顾着
Things with Yu Hao
和余昊的事情
To ignore my mother
才忽略了我妈
That would have happened
才会发生这样的事
Just now
刚才
He showed up just now
刚才他出现在
In front of me
我面前的时候
All I can think about is him
我脑子里全是和他
Pictures together
在一起的画面
But
可是
But with those pictures
可是和那些画面
Stacked together
叠在一起的
It's a picture of my mother seriously ill
是我妈妈病重的画面
I would even think of
我甚至会想到
If my mother can't get it back
如果我妈妈救不回来
I
我
I really don't know
我真的不知道
What should I do
我该怎么办
I just think
我只觉得
I had to be separated from him
我只有和他分开
My mother can get better
我妈妈才能好起来
Coming, coming
来了来了
Let me get you a glass of water
给你倒杯水去
Gong Wenxing
龚文星
Am I really doing something wrong
我是不是真的做错了
I was wrong
我错了
What did I do wrong
我哪做错了
Is it really wrong
真错了吗
Mengmeng
梦梦
I'm worried about Colan
我担心可岚
Want to be with her
想陪陪她
Then I won't go back tonight
那今晚就不回去了
Good
好
I see
我知道了
Bye bye
拜拜
As a child
小时候
My mom always blames my dad
我妈一直怨我爸
Busy with work without accompanying her
忙工作不陪她
I think it's all my dad's fault
我觉得错都在我爸
Grow up
长大了
Work
工作了
I think it was that time again
又觉得是那个时候
My mother is too sensitive
我妈太敏感
Now think about it
现在想想
In fact, they are all wrong
其实他们都错了
If I had known
早知道
People who are not in the same world
不是一个世界的人
Why do you want to be together in the first place
一开始为什么要在一起
Anjie
安捷
Mr. Wang
王总
This document
这份文件
When Yu Zong comes, sign for him
等余总来了给他签字
Good
好
Anjie
安捷
Yu Zongke Lan Jie Meng Jie
余总 可岚姐  梦姐
All are absent
通通不在
I didn't say whether it was a business trip or leave
也没说是出差还是请假
Do you know what's going on
你知道怎么回事吗
Mr. Su has something at home
苏总家里有事
I haven't shown up for so many days
都这么多天没出现
It can't be serious, can it
不会很严重吧
Didn't eat
都没吃
Eat more or less
多少吃点吧
I'll make something to eat myself
我自己去做点吃的
What happened to Su Kelan
苏可岚怎么回事
Say what is not a kind of person
说什么不是一类人
Isn't this deliberately unpleasant
这不故意找不痛快吗
Then who let Yu Haoyi come back
那谁让余昊一回来
I ran to work with Shen Zhilin
就跑去跟沈之琳工作呀
That's because
那是因为
He put his career first
他把事业放在第一位
He acquiesces that others think the same way
他就默认别人也这么想
But for Colan
可是对于可岚来说
More importantly, her mother
更重要的是她妈妈
Her mother is ill in hospital
她妈妈都生病住院了
Yu Hao doesn't go to the hospital
余昊不去医院
Go on a business trip
跑去出差
Then Yu Hao will go
那余昊就算去了
I can't let her mother
也不能让她妈妈
Get better
好起来啊
And
而且
Her mother is ill
她妈妈生病
It's not Yu Hao's fault
也不是余昊的错呀
Is it all right if you break up your hand disease
这分了手病就好了吗
Why are you torturing people like this
你何必这么折磨人
What do you mean by that
你这话什么意思啊
It's all Colan's fault
敢情全是可岚的不对了
And
而且
If it weren't for Yu Hao
要不是因为余昊
Pull Colan
拽着可岚
Auntie, how can this time
阿姨怎么可能这段时间
Don't dare to say anything to Colan
什么都不敢跟可岚说
She is afraid of delay
她是因为怕耽误
She fell in love
她谈恋爱
So you said that the present situation
所以你说现在这种情况
Yu Hao has no responsibility at all
余昊没有半点责任
This Yu Hao is not guilty to death, is he
这余昊也罪不至死吧
Thinking about what will happen in the future
想着以后怎么
Just take care of your aunt together
一起照顾阿姨就行了啊
Split up what hand
分什么手啊
Yu Hao recently treated her
余昊最近对她
Can't she see the change
改变她看不见吗
Hello
喂
I will go tomorrow
我明天会去
Mr. Yu didn't come today
余总今天没来
For fried rice
炒饭用的
It all seems ordinary
都是看似平常
It's very simple
很简单
Ingredients that are readily available
随手就可以获得的食材
You can stir-fry it in a pan
可在锅中一翻炒
Delicious and full
美味又饱腹
Become the easiest happiness to get
变成最容易获得的幸福
And simple
而简单的
Is often the most worthwhile
往往是最值得
Concerned about aftertaste
牵挂回味的
The smell of fireworks in the world
人间烟火味
This dish
这道菜
It's in everyone's memory
每个人的记忆中都有
But what everyone remembers
可每个人记忆中的
They all have different tastes
口味都不同
The taste in your memory
你记忆中的味道
What's the taste of the egg
是什么口感的蛋呢
What ripeness do tomatoes have
什么熟度的番茄呢
Do you want to put sugar in it or not
放不放糖呢
Do you want to put vinegar in it or not
放不放醋呢
Do you want to put soy sauce
放不放酱油呢
Do you want to put onions
放不放葱呢
First discovery
第一次发现
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes outside
外面的番茄炒蛋
It's not as good as when it's delicious at home
不如家里的好吃时
Just know
才知道
The original simple dish
原来那么简单的菜
It can also be so unique
也可以那么独特
I didn't know you liked it
不知道你喜欢吃
What cooked eggs
什么熟度的蛋
So I ordered a well-done one
所以要了一个全熟的
I asked for a soft-boiled one
要了一个溏心的
Fried minced meat with cowpea
泡豇豆炒肉末
And like the kimchi of a family
而喜欢一家的泡菜
Will go from friends to
会从朋友成为
Family
家人
If there is a kitchen
如果有厨房
Can have more such surprises
能有更多这样的惊喜
The theme of this program
这期节目主题
It's the taste of parting
是离别的滋味
The taste of parting
离别的滋味
Is to miss
是想念
Hello
喂
Have you seen Yu Hao lately
你最近见到余昊了吗
I can't find him
我找不着他了
You can't reach Yu Hao
你联系不上余昊了
Yu Hao
余昊
Yu Hao, are you in there
余昊 你在里面吗
Hello, is this property
你好 是物业吗
My friend put himself
我朋友把自己
Locked in the house
锁在屋里了
Could you please open the door
能麻烦来开下门吗
Thank you
谢谢啊
Yu Hao
余昊
Why are you here
你怎么在这
Everyone is looking for him
大家都在找他呢
Eat so much
吃这么多啊
Get up
起来了
You're on your own
你自己一个人
Eat so much
吃了这么多啊
Yu Hao
余昊
Ambulance
救护车